http://www.hi-london.com/terms-of-use

COVID-19 Update: Online & Face-to-Face Classes for Winter 2020/21.HomeAbout UsOur EthosOur TeamOur AlumniCoursesEnglish for ChildrenEnglish for TeensEnglish for AdultsSchedule & FeesEnglish Courses ChildrenEnglish Courses TeensEnglish Courses AdultsContact UsRegisterOur BlogHi-New-YorkMoreHomeAbout UsOur EthosOur TeamOur AlumniCoursesEnglish for ChildrenEnglish for TeensEnglish for AdultsSchedule & FeesEnglish Courses ChildrenEnglish Courses TeensEnglish Courses AdultsContact UsRegisterOur BlogHi-New-YorkHomeAbout UsCoursesSchedule & FeesContact UsRegisterOur BlogHi-New-York
Terms of UsePlease read these terms of use carefully before using this website ("Site"). By using this Site, you are agreeing to these terms of use. If you do not agree to these terms of use, you should not use the Site. We reserve the right to change these terms at any time. Any changes will be posted on this Site. Your continued use of this Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you agree to those changes. Website Owner
This Site is owned and operated by Horizon International Ltd., trading as Hi-London ("Hi-London", "our", "us", and "we"). Horizon International Ltd. is an English limited company with a registered place of business at 96 Kensington High Street, London W8 4SG, United Kingdom . Our email address is info@hi-london.com, and our phone number is +44 (0)20 3667 8788. Disclaimer The materials on this Site are provided "as is" and without warranties of any kind either express or implied. Horizon International Ltd. does not warrant that this Site or any part of it will be available in an uninterrupted or error-free way, that defects will be corrected, or that this Site or the server that makes such materials available is free of viruses or other harmful components. We do not warrant or make any representations regarding the use or the results of the use of the materials on this Site in terms of their correctness, accuracy, reliability, or otherwise. You assume the entire cost of all necessary servicing, repair, or correction of your computer equipment following your use of this Site.The main language of the Site is English. If you choose to use an automatic translation service such as Google Translate, you do so subject to its terms of use and at your own risk. We do not accept any liability for any loss or damage you may suffer as a result of any inaccurate or misleading translation produced by such a service. These limitations of liability do not apply to the extent that they are prohibited by any applicable law. Copyright & Trademarks Except where otherwise indicated, the copyright in all material appearing on this Site (including but not limited to all text, graphics, drawings, logos, photographs, videos, and sound recordings) is owned by Horizon International Ltd. All trademarks, service marks and trade names of Horizon International Ltd. used in this Site (including but not limited to Hi-London and the Hi-London logo) are trademarks or registered trademarks of Horizon International Ltd. Other trademarks, service marks, and trade names belong to their respective owners. You may not use, copy, reproduce, republish, upload, post, transmit, distribute, or modify any material (whether protected by copyright or trademark law) owned by us in any way without our prior written consent. The use of our copyright material or trade marks on any other site or in any computer network is prohibited without our prior written consent. We prohibit the use of our trademarks as a link on other web sites unless we have approved such a link in writing in advance. Restrictions on Use of Site and Materials
Permission is granted to view, electronically copy, and print in hard copy portions of this Site for the sole purpose of using this Site as an electronic brochure, making a registration, or communicating with us, provided you keep intact all copyright and other proprietary notices. With these exceptions, no material from this Site may be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way. Modification of the materials on this Site or use of the materials for any other purpose, including but not limited to use on any other Site or in any computer network, is prohibited.Any software downloaded from the Site, including any files and images incorporated in or generated by the software, and data accompanying the software is licensed to you by Horizon International Ltd. or the relevant owner of the software or other material, and its use is subject to the terms of the licence agreement included in the installation package. Neither we nor any such relevant owner transfers title to the software or other material to you. Except to the extent required by any applicable law, you may not redistribute, sell, decompile, reverse engineer, disassemble, or otherwise reduce the software to a human-readable form.
You are prohibited from transmitting to or from this Site any unlawful, threatening, defamatory, obscene, inflammatory or pornographic material or any other material that could give rise to any civil or criminal liability under any applicable law.User-Generated ContentThis website may include information and materials uploaded by other users of the Site, including to bulletin boards and chat rooms. This information and these materials have not been verified or approved by us. The views expressed by other users on our Site do not represent our views or values.If you wish to complain about content uploaded by other users, please contact us at info@hi-london.com.Limitation of LiabilityHorizon International Ltd. makes no warranties or representations as to the accuracy of the information on this Site, and we assume no liability or responsibility for any errors or omissions in its contents. Under no circumstances, including, but not limited to, negligence, shall we be liable for any damages of any description resulting from the use of, or the inability to use, this Site or its content. These limitations of liability do not apply to the extent that they are prohibited by any applicable law.Links to Other Web Sites
There may be links to other Sites from this Site that take you outside our service. Such other Sites are beyond our control, and we do not accept any responsibility for any loss or damage you may suffer as a result of using such other Sites. These other Sites may send their own cookies to you, collect data, or solicit personal information. While we strive to protect our users' personal information and privacy, these other Sites may not do so, and you use them at your own risk. Course RegistrationsAny programme registered is subject to our Registration Terms and Conditions which are available by link from our Site and invoice prior to paying for your programme. Please click here to see our Registration Terms and Conditions.Complaints If you have a complaint or are unhappy with any aspect of this Site, please email info@hi-london.com.Any complaint will be acknowledged within 5 working days and a resolution or explanation proposed within 15 working days. All complaints will be properly investigated and dealt with in confidence. No information supplied will be used for any purpose other than to respond to the complaint.
TerminationThese terms are effective until terminated by either party. You may terminate these terms at any time by destroying all materials obtained from this Site and all related documentation and all copies and installations thereof, whether made under these terms or otherwise. These terms will terminate immediately on notice from Horizon International Ltd. if in its sole discretion you fail to comply with any term or provision of these terms. Upon termination, you must destroy all materials obtained from this Site and all copies thereof, whether made under these terms or otherwise. PrivacyInformation you transmit through this Site is subject to Horizon International Ltd.’s Privacy Policy and remains our property. Please click here to see our Privacy Policy. We will make commercially reasonable efforts to protect your personal information and privacy, but we cannot guarantee that any information you transmit to us over the internet will not be monitored or intercepted in the course of transmission. Accordingly, if you transmit information to us over the internet, you do so at your own risk.Entire Agreement With the exception of our Registration Terms and Conditions which apply to programmes registered, these terms are the entire agreement between you and Horizon International Ltd. with respect to the use of this Site and supersede any prior understandings or agreements (written or oral).CopyrightExcept where otherwise indicated, all Site contents, design, photographs, graphics, and text are Copyright © 2020, Horizon International Ltd. Governing Law & JurisdictionAny claim relating to, and the use of, this Site and the materials contained herein is governed by the laws of England and Wales applicable to contracts wholly performed therein, and is subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the English and Welsh courts. April 2020 Edition
Contact us for more information
Terms of Use | Privacy Policy | Registration TermsHorizon International Ltd.
